[{"answer": "Well, of course, we want health care for everyone.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "Let me start by asking you why are you so implacably opposed to universal health care for all?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Well, absolutely no one can fathom why he came up with the decision that he did.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "Why has he flown against all conservative thinking if that's what it is?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "Do you have car insurance?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "I have car insurance because I have an investment in my car and I want to make sure that I can hold on to that investment.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Who told you to?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Well, I said it in the beginning of my remarks.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "What is the difference between Americans being forced by law to have insurance to drive a car and being forced by law to have insurance for their health?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "Well, again, the compare and contrast couldn't be more stark between Barack Obama and Mitt Romney because when voters go into the polls this November, they can vote for Barack Obama who will keep government health care, which is government control over our lives in health care and what is called a taxmageddon that is coming upon us.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "You can call me bemused of the British isles, Michele Bachmann, but what is the difference?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Well, that's simple.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "What is the ideological difference between that and what Barack Obama has done?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "No, that isn't what he said at all.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "ORGAN: See, I'm even more bemused now because unless I'm going completely mad, he's basically saying that what he did in Massachusetts could be done just as effectively on a national level, isn't he?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "Well, it's very clear from the legislation it was not called a tax.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "Is this a tax or is it a penalty?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "Well, I've already answered that question.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "Is it a tax or as Mitt Romney says a penalty?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "I think that American people are seeing the very clear contrast between Barack Obama's failed policies and Mitt Romney's expertise and know-how.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Do you think?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "I don't agree with it at all because if you look at Mitt Romney's history, very smart guy with a very optimistic savvy message and people know that they can trust him on dealing with the economy.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Well, one thing I know about Mitt Romney he's made excellent decisions in the past when it comes to running organizations.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "What would you say to him?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "Well, that's something for the campaign to answer on.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "Are you being vetted at the moment?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "I'd say, Piers, that there's a reason that a vast majority of Americans still oppose Obamacare.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "What do you say?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "And going back to the point about -- and going back to the point -- well, the point is if you don't like what I'm saying and if you don't like the fact that you're making up facts, then just hear me out.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "What is the point to this?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "It's not the -- it's not the --", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "What facts did I make up exactly?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "It's not that -- don't be so catty.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "What fact did I make up exactly?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "As I was saying, it's not the largest tax increase in the history of the United States, as you and your cohorts like to say.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Commerce?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "Some people do dispute that but I've also seen the statistics that there'll be 813 billion plus in new taxes and some would say that's the largest tax increase.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "No one disputes that, right?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "Let me ask you a quick question?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "Kellyanne, do you have car insurance?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Well, to me it was, you know, Los Angeles sort of represented a sort of tarnished elegance back when we were working on this record and these songs back in 1976.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "What was it to you?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Well, you know, what -- what I looked at now, you know, I grew up in Detroit, Michigan.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "When you look at modern American and the way America has developed since the song, what do you think of what's going on now in terms in terms of happy people taken excess too far, do you think?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "Well, you know, when Barack Obama got elected, some friends of mine and I, we looked at each other and we said now we're going to find out how broke it really is.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "Is there a simple answer now?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "Do you think there's merit to that?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "It's been very good to me.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "Isn't it?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "It's pretty something.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "Isn't that incredible?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "I'd have had to be frugal, but.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "Could you just retire and lived off the proceeds of Hotel California, the single?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "Well, back in the '70s, when you put a record out it was a pretty simple formula.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "How has it exchanged?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "Well, you know I have my favorite records.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "What is the song, of all the songs that you've ever been involved with, what is the one, if I said, write, Glenn, you've got five minutes to live, you can play one song to be remembered by, the defining song?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "I loved one of these nights.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "What's your number one?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I love Adele.", "docId": "120702pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "And who of all the acts out there now, who's the one that excites you, the modern crowd?", "qSentId": 650}]